Chris Coenen Collection on General Tom Thumb MS254
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Chris Coenen Collection on General Tom Thumb
circa 1750 -- 2010
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
MS254
41.09 Linear Feet 13 oversize boxes; 4 rolled item boxes/tubes; 3 card boxes; 2 half letter size document boxes; 2 framed items; 1 letter size document box; 1 legal size document box; 1 oversize flat file; 1 stereoscope.
This collection contains material related to P. T. Barnum and General Tom Thumb collected by Christopher Coenen, including artifacts, cabinet cards, cartes-de-visite, printed ephemera, printed materials, photographs, and stereographs.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Christopher Coenen A'71, 2018 and 2021, accession numbers MS-2019-048 and MS-2022-009.
Appraisal
Books related to P. T. Barnum and General Tom Thumb were not accessioned.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in six series:, Artifacts, Cabinet cards, Cartes-de-visite, Printed ephemera, Printed materials, and Stereographs.
Biographical / Historical
Christopher Joseph Coenen attended Tufts from 1967 to 1971 and graduated from the Tufts University School of Arts, Sciences, and Engineering with a B.S. degree. Majoring in biology, he was a frequent visitor to Barnum Hall and Jumbo, the stuffed hide of an elephant donated by P. T. Barnum. In 1968, Dr. Russell Carpenter, a professor of biology and curator of Barnum Hall, gave a closing lecture on Barnum and Jumbo to his freshman zoology class. Upon graduation and completing research in the Bahamas the following year, Coenen entered the teaching profession. He taught for 42 years at the Berkshire School and Franklin Academy. Coenen's interest in antique photographs eventually led him to collect material related to Charles Stratton (General Tom Thumb). Coenen retired from teaching and resides in western Massachusetts.
Related Materials
Collection on P. T. Barnum, 1818 -- 2009. Tufts University. Digital Collections and Archives. Medford, MA.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains material related to P. T. Barnum and General Tom Thumb collected by Christopher Coenen. The collection contains artifacts, including ceramic plates, paper dolls, a board game, coins, autographs, and slides; cabinet cards; cartes-de-visite; printed ephemera and printed materials, including clippings, copies of daguerreotypes and lithographs, advertisements, fliers, sheet music, brochures, and booklets; and stereographs. Item-level description was provided by the donor and has not been verified.
Content Warning
This finding aid contains language that may be offensive or outdated. Because such language is in direct transcription of materials or donor-supplied metadata, it has not yet been reviewed or changed. Keeping this language intact can potentially tell us important things about bigotry and bias in a particular historical context. It can also preserve terms formerly applied by a group to self-identify that have since fallen out of common usage.
More specifically, this collection contains ableist images and language, particularly related to dwarfism, racist imagery including blackface, and materials related to phrenology. For more information on DCA's content warning policy please visit our website.
Biographical / Historical
Charles Sherwood Stratton, better known by his stage name "General Tom Thumb," was born January 4, 1838 in Bridgeport, Connecticut to Sherwood Edward Stratton and Cynthia Thompson. Stratton was an average sized baby at birth, but his growth slowed at around six months of age when he was approximately 25 inches tall. He eventually grew to 40 inches tall.
P. T. Barnum heard of Stratton and contacted his parents. Stratton's parents agreed to allow their four-year-old son to perform and be on display at Barnum's American Museum in New York City in 1842. At the age of five, Stratton was taken on tour across the United States, singing, dancing, and impersonating characters such as Cupid and Napoleon Bonaparte. In 1844, Barnum took Stratton to perform in England and France, including two performances for Queen Victoria. Stratton returned to the United States after the three-year tour and continued to perform for American audiences as part of an exhibit of "human curiosities."
In 1863, Stratton married Lavinia Warren, who was also a little person who he met while working at Barnum's American Museum. The wedding took place at Grace Episcopal Church in New York City and was widely covered in the media. George Washington Morrison Nutt, known by his stage name "Commodore Nutt," was the best man, and Warren's sister Minnie Warren was a bridesmaid. Approximately 10,000 guests attended the wedding reception. Stratton and Warren were received by President Abraham Lincoln at the White House after their wedding and then traveled to Europe and what is today Bangladesh.
Stratton continued to perform until 1878. He died of a stroke in Middleboro, Massachusetts on July 15, 1883. He was buried in Mountain Grove Cemetery in Bridgeport, Connecticut.
Biographical / Historical
Phineas Taylor (P. T.) Barnum (1810 - 1891), was a showman and circus entrepreneur who also served on the board of Trustees of Tufts College and as a benefactor of the institution in its early years.
Barnum was born in Bethel, Connecticut on July 5, 1810, to Philo F. Barnum, a farmer and shopkeeper, and Irena Taylor. He held many jobs as a youth, including herding cattle, selling theater tickets, and publishing the abolitionist newspaper The Herald of Freedom (1831-1834). Barnum married seamstress Charity Hallett in 1829, and they had four daughters.
In 1835 Barnum purchased the right to exhibit the elderly enslaved woman Joice Heth, as the supposed 161-year-old nurse of George Washington, at Niblo's Gardens in New York City. He then led a small traveling circus through the South and West, and engaged in a number of unsuccessful business ventures. In 1841 Barnum bought and re-opened the American Museum in New York City. Exhibits included the Feegee [sic] mermaid, the bearded lady, and the "Egress," along with fossils and natural history specimens. Barnum's half-brother Philo introduced him to the dwarf Charles Sherwood Stratton in 1842, and Barnum hired Stratton as an exhibit under the name General Tom Thumb. Barnum and Stratton made several tours to England and Europe (1844, 1858).
From 1851 to 1857 Barnum was one of the founding trustees of the new Universalist institution, Tufts College (founded in 1852 and opened to students in 1854). After being elected to the Trustees in 1851, Barnum resigned in 1857, because his busy schedule of tours precluded his attendance at board meetings. Between 1882 and 1884, Barnum anonymously gave over $50,000 to Tufts College to build the Barnum Museum of Natural History. He also left over $30,000 in his will to build two subsequent wings. In 1889, Barnum donated the mounted skin of Jumbo the elephant to the Barnum Museum at Tufts. Barnum hoped that the publicity might be useful to the college, and Jumbo became the school mascot.
In the 1870s Barnum organized the "Greatest Show on Earth," which traveled by train through the United States and Canada. In 1881 he joined his business rivals to form the Barnum and Bailey Circus. He died in Bridgeport, Connecticut on April 7, 1891.
Biographical / Historical
Lavinia Warren Stratton was born Mercy Lavinia Bump on October 31, 1842 in Middleborough, Massachusetts, to Huldah Pierce Warren and James Sullivan Bump. Lavinia, as well as her sister Minnie, had a form of dwarfism.
Warren began teaching at the age of 16 and later took a job singing and dancing on a Mississippi showboat owned by a cousin. The program, "The Museum of Living Wonders," billed her as the "Lilliputian Queen." Warren danced, sang show tunes, and occasionally performed a double act with a woman with gigantism, Silvia Hardy, from Maine. In 1862, P. T. Barnum met Warren and invited her to work at the American Museum in New York City.
In 1863, Warren married Charles Stratton, known as General Tom Thumb, who was also a little person whom she met while working at Barnum's American Museum. The wedding took place at Grace Episcopal Church in New York City and was widely covered in the media. George Washington Morrison Nutt, known by his stage name "Commodore Nutt," was the best man, and Warren's sister Minnie Warren was a bridesmaid. Approximately 10,000 guests attended the wedding reception. Warren and Stratton were received by President Abraham Lincoln at the White House after their wedding and then traveled to Europe and what is today Bangladesh.
After Stratton's death, Warren married Count Primo Magri. They operated a roadside stand in Middleborough, Massachusetts that featured other little people. Warren appeared alongside Magri in a 1915 silent film, "The Lilliputian's Courtship."
Warren died on November 25, 1919 and was buried next to Stratton in Mountain Grove Cemetery in Bridgeport, Connecticut.
Biographical / Historical
Count Primo Magri, also known as Count Rosebud, was born in Italy in 1840. Magri came to the United States in 1878. He married Lavinia Warren Stratton in 1885. They operated a roadside stand in Middleborough, Massachusetts that featured other little people. Magri appeared with Warren in a 1915 silent film, "The Lilliputian's Courtship." He died in Middleborough, Massachusetts in 1920.
Biographical / Historical
Huldah Pierce Warren Bump, better known as Minnie Warren, was born June 2, 1849 in Middleborough, Massachusetts to Huldah Pierce Warren and James Sullivan Bump. Minnie, as well as her sister Lavinia, had a form of dwarfism. Warren performed as a singer and was married to Edmund Newell, a little person who was also a paid performer for P. T. Barnum. Warren died on July 23, 1878 due to complications from childbirth. She is buried in Nemasket Hill Cemetery in Middleborough, Massachusetts.
Biographical / Historical
George Washington Morrison Nutt, best known by his stage name Commodore Nutt, was born in Manchester, New Hampshire to Major Rodnia Nutt and Maria Nutt. Nutt was a little person who performed in circuses and was hired by P. T. Barnum to appear in the American Museum in New York City. Nutt performed internationally with General Tom Thumb, Lavinia Warren, and Minnie Warren from 1869 to 1872. Upon returning from touring, Nutt ceased working for Barnum. He toured with a comic opera company, organized a variety show on the west coast of the United States, and ran saloons in Oregon and California.
In 1879, Nutt married Lilian Elston of Redwood City, California. He returned to New York City and died of Bright's disease, a historical classification of kidney disease, in May 1881.
Circus performers; People with Dwarfism; Barnum, P. T. (Phineas Taylor)
- Artifacts, 1750 -- 1996; MS254.000007
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains artifacts related to Tom Thumb, including slides, prints, autographs, paper dolls, ceramic plates, medals, souvenir charms, cards, a board game, a doll, and a hack saw frame.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged in received order.
  - Autograph; Charles Stratton, 1860; MS254.000008 (Box 12)
    Autograph
  - Autograph; Countess M. Lavinia Magri, 1900; MS254.000009 (Box 12)
    Autograph with greeting card
  - Autograph; Count Primo Magri, 1890; MS254.000010 (Box 12)
  - Autograph;Charles S. Stratton, 1882; MS254.000011 (Box 12)
    From autograph album
  - Autograph: Count Rosebud,; Primo Magri, 1882; MS254.000012 (Box 12)
  - Autograph; Baron Littlefinger; Ernesto Magri, 1882; MS254.000013 (Box 12)
  - Autograph; Maor E. Newell, 1882; MS254.000014 (Box 12)
  - Autograph; Miss Eliza Nestel, 1882; MS254.000015 (Box 12)
  - Autograph; Miss Jennie Quigley, 1882; MS254.000016 (Box 12)
  - Autograph; General C. R. Decker, 1882; MS254.000017 (Box 12)
  - Autograph; Commodore Foote, 1882; MS254.000018 (Box 12)
  - Autograph; Minnie Warren, 1877; MS254.000019 (Box 12)
  - Autograph; Count Primo Magri; Countess M L Magri, 1893; MS254.000020 (Box 12)
    On Palace Hotel, Denver stationary
  - Autograph; Charles S. Stratton, 1873; MS254.000021 (Box 12)
    From a hotel registry
  - Autograph; Minnie Warren, 1877; MS254.000022 (Box 12)
  - Autograph; Count Primo Magri; Countess M L Magri, 1892; MS254.000023 (Box 12)
    Autographs
  - Autograph:Baron L. Ernesto Magri, 1892; MS254.000024 (Box 12)
  - Autograph; P.T. Barnum, 1879; MS254.000025 (Box 12)
  - Letter descibing a visit to Tom Thumb show, 1843; MS254.000026 (Box 12)
    Letter with Tom Thumb reference
  - Letter describing early Barnum Circus and Tom Thumb, 1930; MS254.000027 (Box 12)
    Letter with Tom Thumb reference and Barnum Circus reference
  - Contract for travel on The Rio Grande and Southern Railroad, 1893; MS254.000028 (Box 12)
    Contract for transporting the Mrs. General Tom Thumb Theatrical Company, for passage between Rico and Durango
  - Western Union Telegram from Lavinia to the Beaumonts, 1891; MS254.000029 (Box 12)
    The Beaumonts, Owego, NY; Lavinia asks them to meet
  - Letter from Henry C. Potter; autographed, 1871; MS254.000030 (Box 12)
    Potter was involved in the Tom Thumb Wedding; discussing Italy
  - Envelope from the Metropolitan Hotel, 1864; MS254.000031 (Box 12)
    The Metroppolitan Hotel was the site of the Tom Thumb Wedding reception
  - Paper doll; Mrs. Tom Thumb; Boston Sunday Post, 1946; MS254.000032 (Box 12)
    From a section of the Boston Sunday Post; unknown date
  - Paper Doll; General Tom Thumb; Mc Loughlin Bros., 1865; MS254.000033 (Box 12)
    Cut out paper dolls of Tom Thumb with varous outfits
  - Paper doll; Commodore Nutt; McLoughlin Bros., 1865; MS254.000034 (Box 12)
    Cut out paper dolls of Commodore Nutt with various outfits
  - Paper doll: Minnie Warren; McLoughlin Bros., 1865; MS254.000035 (Box 12)
    Cut out paper dolls of Minnie Warren with various outfits
  - Paper doll: Mrs. Tom Thumb; McLoughlin Bros., 1865; MS254.000036 (Box 12)
    Uncut booklet of paper dolls of Lavinia Warren
  - Paper doll; Mrs. Tom Thumb; McLoughlin Bros. II, 1865; MS254.000037 (Box 12)
    Several outfits
  - Paper doll; Tom Thumb Baby; McLoughlin Bros., 1865; MS254.000038 (Box 12)
    Cut out paper dolls of the Thumb baby
  - First Cover letter commemorating Tom and Lavinia's visit to Abraham Lincoln; 2/13/63, 1963; MS254.000039 (Box 12)
    Celebrating the one hundreth anniversary of their visit to Lincoln shortly after their marriage in 1863
  - Autograph; Tom Thumb; with calling card; 5/11/49, 1849; MS254.000040 (Box 12)
    Mounted signature and miniature calling card
  - Autograph; Tom Thumb to Mlle. Durand; 6/22/45, 1845; MS254.000041 (Box 12)
    Autograph by seven year old Tom Thumb to Mlle. Durand
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.: Watercolor of Tom Thumb, 1845; MS254.000042 (Box 12)
    Date unknown but on one of his visits to Europe.
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.: Tom as Gentleman, 1858; MS254.000043 (Box 12)
    From the series taken by Whitney of Norwalk
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.: Watercolor of Tom as Napoleon, 1845; MS254.000044 (Box 12)
    Small watercolor of Tom Thumb as Napoleon
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:detail of larger print, 1845; MS254.000045 (Box 12)
    Detail of larger print with Thumb as Highlander
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:detail of Tom as Highlander from print, 1845; MS254.000046 (Box 12)
    Large image of Tom from print
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:Belgian Royal Family, 1845; MS254.000047 (Box 12)
    Detail from larger print
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:Music sheet; Minnie Warrens Quadrille, 1845; MS254.000048 (Box 12)
    Sheet cover with egraviing of Minnie and Nutt
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:French engraving of Tom with three ladiies, 1845; MS254.000049 (Box 12)
    Sheet music? 1845
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:print with Tom Thumb as Highlander, 1845; MS254.000050 (Box 12)
    Larger print with details along the side
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:sheet music with engraving of Tom and Victoria, circa 1845; MS254.000051 (Box 12)
    Comic song
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:Le General Tom Pouce a Paris, 1845; MS254.000052 (Box 12)
    Engraving of Tom being held with his performing platform in the background.
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:stereo of Tom, Barnum and Lady, 1858; MS254.000053 (Box 12)
    British stereo from the second visit
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:Barnum/Thumb display at the Theatre Museum,, Covent Garden, 1995; MS254.000054 (Box 12)
    Display at the Theatre Musem with poster for Tom Thumb circa 1864
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:Broadside for Tom's performance after coming back England., 1846; MS254.000055 (Box 12)
    Playing at Egyptian Hall
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:Tom Thumb and the giantess, 1845; MS254.000056 (Box 12)
    Detail from a larger print
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:comic song spoofing Barnum, 1845; MS254.000057 (Box 12)
    Humbug
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:Tom Thumb astonishing the British Lion; sketch, circa 1845; MS254.000058 (Box 12)
    drawing of Tom Thumb thumbing his nose at the British lion
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.: Long Champs Parade, 1845; MS254.000059 (Box 12)
    Barnum managed an invitation for Tom To ride his carriage in the famous parade in Paris
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:stereo detail, 1858; MS254.000060 (Box 12)
    Detail of stereo
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:stereo detai, colored, 1858; MS254.000061 (Box 12)
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:engraving of French midget, 1750; MS254.000062 (Box 12)
    Date unknown of a dwarf
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:engraving of bearded lady; BarbarabUrslerin, 1750; MS254.000063 (Box 12)
    Bearde lady Barbara Urslerin
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:Horned man, 1750; MS254.000064 (Box 12)
    Horned man; unknown date
  - Slide: Victoria & Albert, Theater Museum, Blythe Rd.:Reception by the King and Queen of Belgium, 1845; MS254.000065 (Box 12)
    Recption by the King and Queen of Belgium from a larger print
  - Slide: Barnum's grpoup of prodigies and acts, 1890; MS254.000066 (Box 12)
    Print of sideshow acts from the circus
  - Slide: Lavinia's home in Middleboro, 1995; MS254.000067 (Box 12)
    Possibly Lavinia's birthplace; located across the street from the house she and Tom built
  - Slide: Lavinia and Primo outside the Thumb House in Middleboro, 1890; MS254.000068 (Box 12)
    Lavinia and Primo in front of the house
  - Slide: Edwin Newell, 1878; MS254.000069 (Box 12)
    Minnie's husband
  - Slide: Figi Mermaid, 1840; MS254.000070 (Box 12)
    Engraving of the mermaid
  - Slide: Lilliputian group with Goshen, Rodnia Nutt, etc., 1875; MS254.000071 (Box 12)
    Members of a Lilliputian troop
  - Slide: Lavinia Warren's brothers, 1875; MS254.000072 (Box 12)
    Lavinia's brothers
  - Slide: Lavinia Warren's sisiters, 1875; MS254.000073 (Box 12)
    Lavinia's sisters
  - Slide: Barnum and Essler, 1858; MS254.000074 (Box 12)
    Barnum was reportedly sweet on the dancer, Fanny Essler
  - Slide: Cover of a book on Barnum by Arthur Saxton, 1990; MS254.000075 (Box 12)
    Book cover with Barnum enterprises
  - Slide: Tom Thumb as Robinson Crusoe; ambrotype, 1855; MS254.000076 (Box 12)
    Tom Thumb dressed as Robinson Crusoe; ambrotype
  - Slide: Print of Tom Thumb at the White House?, 1844; MS254.000077 (Box 12)
    Early Tom Thumb; visiting the White House (?) and president...?
  - Slide: Tom Thumb glove, 1865; MS254.000078 (Box 12)
    Unknown date; glove compared to quarter
  - Slide: ambrotype of Tom Thumb and man, 1855; MS254.000079 (Box 12)
    Ambrotype out of case
  - Slide: Back of ambrotype on Tom and man, 1855; MS254.000080 (Box 12)
    Backof ambrotype
  - Slide: Front of ambrotype of Tom and man, 1855; MS254.000081 (Box 12)
    Front of ambrotype
  - Slide: Tom and man, 1848; MS254.000082 (Box 12)
    Tom and man
  - Slide: Tom and young girl; ambrotype, 1855; MS254.000083 (Box 12)
    Tom and girl; ambrotype
  - Slide: Primo Magri auctioning off Tom Thumb memorabilia; Middleboro, 1920, MS254.000084 (Box 12)
    After Lavinia's death in 1919, Primo wanted to return to Italy; he auctioned off some of the artifacts but died shortly after; original at MHS
  - Slide: Lindencroft where Tom proposed to Lavinia, 1865; MS254.000085 (Box 12)
    Supposedly, Tom proposed to Lavinia one Saturday night at Lindencroft
  - Slide: PT Barnum as "The Humbug", 1855; MS254.000086 (Box 12)
    Unknown date of parody of Barnum
  - Slide: Waldemere, Barnum's estate at Seaside Park, Bridgeport, 1870; MS254.000087 (Box 12)
    Waldemere
  - Slide: Winter in front of Barnum's Museum on Broadway, 1865; MS254.000088 (Box 12)
    Famous print of Brodadway in winter
  - Slide: View from St. Pauls of Brady's Studio across from the Museum, 1865; MS254.000089 (Box 12)
    Unknown date; view from the steeple
  - Slide: Album presented to Lavinia by E. & H. T. Anthony; BPL, 1865; MS254.000090 (Box 12)
    Album presented by Anthony to Lavinia; Anthony's printed the thousands of CDV's sold by the couple; in the collection of the Bridgeport Public Library, Hisorical Room
  - Slide: Baby; comparison of three CDV's, 1864; MS254.000091 (Box 12)
    There are three early photos of the hoax baby; normaly cameras would have taken four negatives; one must have been ruined or broken
  - Slide: Older Lavinia in a chair, 1918; MS254.000092 (Box 12)
    Old Lavinia
  - Slide: Tom in carriage, 1858; MS254.000093 (Box 12)
    From a series by Whitney of Norwalk/Bridgeport
  - Slide: Early Lavinia Warren; probably tintype, 1860; MS254.000094 (Box 12)
    early lavinia
  - Slide: Snaphsots of Lavinia and Primo at home from an album, 1915; MS254.000095 (Box 12)
    Lavinia and Primo at home with Ernesto
  - Slide: Print of Iranistan, Barnum's Home, 1850; MS254.000096 (Box 12)
    Print of Barnum's elaborate home which burned
  - Slide: Painting of the Barnum Museum fire, 1865; MS254.000097 (Box 12)
    Painting of the fire
  - Slide: Sketch of the Nimrod, the steamship Charles and his mother took to New York City to work at the Museum, 1845; MS254.000098 (Box 12)
    Nimrod was the ferry Charles and his mother took to NYC in 1843
  - Slide: Tom Thumb and man:, 1865; MS254.000099 (Box 12)
  - Slide: poster advertising Barnum lecture; England, 1858; MS254.000100 (Box 12)
    Poster advertising PT Barnum
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Ernesto Magri and wife, 1878; MS254.000101 (Box 12)
    Ernesto and wife; she went back to Italy
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Oil painting of Commodore Nutt in the MPL, 1875; MS254.000102 (Box 12)
    Painting in the Library
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Oil painting of Minnie Warren in the MPL, 1875; MS254.000103 (Box 12)
    Painting in the library
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): At Primo's Pastime, 1905; MS254.000104 (Box 12)
    In front of the store in Middleboro
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Primo and dog, 1910; MS254.000105 (Box 12)
    Primo and dog
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Nemasket Grange, Middleboro, 1910; MS254.000106 (Box 12)
    Nemasket Grange
  - Slide, Middleboro Public Library (MPL): Lavinia and Minnie dresssed, 1875; MS254.000107 (Box 12)
    In similar dresses